我得带一个回家吃
I may have to take one of these little guys home.
克莱尔  你找到我借你的保鲜盒了吗
Claire, did you ever find that Tupperware I lent you?
亲爱的  跟你说过一百遍了
Sweetie, for the hundredth time,
我还给你了  记得吗
I gave it back to you, remember?
我是记得你说过一百遍
I remember you telling me a hundred times,
可我现在都只能用塑料袋盛豌豆汤
yet my pea soup is in baggies.
你检查过车子吗
Did you check your car?
在那个
In the...
后备箱里
Trunk.
上次你就是在那里找到了
Because that's where you found that thing
那个你以为早就给我了的东西
that you thought that you gave me long time ago,
-那个  那个  -披萨刀
- the... the... - Pizza cutter.
-是的  那次是我错了  -就一团塑料而已
- Yes, I was wrong that time. I-- - It's a piece of plastic.
你把早午餐毁了
You're ruining brunch.
别想太多了  小卡
Don't sweat it, Cam.
我也老是忘事儿
I forget things all the time.
比如我就老是记不住
Like I can never remember the name
我喜欢的那个天气播报员的名字
of that weather guy that I liked. Uh...